SERGIO LOMBANA

Software Developer

- 4168268035 sergiolombana101@gmail.com Toronto
- http://sergio-lombana.com/

SUMMARY

Computer Programming graduate with excellent communication skills and 3+ years of experience seeking an industry opportunity to put into practice the knowledge acquired during college studies. Hard-working, time-effective and detail-oriented individual. Looking for a company to demonstrate skills and benefit their processes.

PROJECTS

Inventory Management System

 MEAN stack application in charge of managing Shiva Exports Ltda inventory processes. Built with high quantity of JavaScript to provide user interactivity. Project was built using all the Agile Methodologies process.

React Productivity Assistant

 React Native Mobile application. The app keeps track of your todo lists and tasks and manages your calendar, habit and goals. It also notifies you of any important event or notification in any of your social media platforms.

PHP Employee Management System

-Built with PHP and the Laravel framework. It is an application the helps the manager to organize employee's schedule, delegate tasks and track punctuality as well as perform CRUD operations. It was built using MySQL for data persistence.

EDUCATION

Computer Programmer Analyst 2018 - 2020

George Brown College

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript	Node.js	● PHP
• Javascript	• Nouc.js	• 1 1 11

• React.js	Python	Github
 Δngular 	● Bootstran	MySOI

● Jquery ● SCSS ● OOP

EXPERIENCE

Computer Programming Tutor

George Brown College

09/2019 - 04/2020 - Toronto

- Helped an average of 10 students a week with Web Development queries
- Created programming challenges for students twice a week

Student Advisor (Peer-coach)

George Brown College

09/2018 - 04/2020 - Toronto

- Tutored web programming students
- Delivered workshops on soft skills
- Advised students on Resume writing strategies

Waiter

Fukui Sushi

06/2019 - 09/2019 - Toronto

- Assisted in training of new waiters
- Memorized menu containing 50 items
- Ensured restaurant was following cleaning procedures.